<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:59 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beta.gatling.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Login</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/login/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:04 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/login/</guid><description>In order to log in, you need an account with the same username as your GitHub account.
If you&amp;rsquo;re the root administrator, we&amp;rsquo;ve already created your account.
Otherwise, please reach out to your root administrator to create your account.
Pressing the Signup with GitHub button will redirect you to GitHub, where you will be asked to authorize the application.
You need to authorize it. We only ask access to your profile.</description></item><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/overview/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:04 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/overview/</guid><description>Once you are logged in, you are now able to navigate using the FrontLine navigation bar on the left side.
FrontLine is composed of:
Profile, manage account settings
Users, manage users information, teams and permissions - accessible to system admin
Teams, manage teams - accessible to system admin
API Tokens, manage token to access the API - accessible to system admin</description></item><item><title>Profile</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/profile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:23 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/profile/</guid><description>Accessing your profile You can view your profile at any time by clicking on the My Profile button in the navigation bar.
The information displayed are the following:
Username First and Last name Mail address Different roles To update your profile, modify the fields you want to change, then click on the button Update your information.
You can&amp;rsquo;t update your username here. You need to ask a System Admin to change your roles on the Users Admin page.</description></item><item><title>Artifact Generation</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/artifact_gen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:50:32 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/artifact_gen/</guid><description>Generating Artifacts for FrontLine FrontLine deploys packages containing your compiled Simulations and resources. Those packages have to be generated upstream. FrontLine is compatible with Gatling 3.3, 3.4 and 3.5.
Gatling zip bundle Please copy the artifact.sh or artifact.bat files in the bin directory of your Gatling unzipped bundle. Those files will be shipped in the bundle in a future official Gatling release.
Please run the script matching your operating system and generate the target/artifact.</description></item><item><title>Artifact Configuration</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/artifact_conf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/artifact_conf/</guid><description>Managing To access the Artifacts section, click on Artifacts in the navbar.
The Simulations view contains all the artifacts you have configured with the given name, team, and filename of uploaded artifact if not empty.
Gatling version of the artifact is displayed in a badge next to the filename.
&amp;#x1f4a1; Artifacts uploaded before the upload validation has been implemented may have a &amp;ldquo;corrupted&amp;rdquo; badge: check how to generate an artifact, and upload it again.</description></item><item><title>Simulations</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/simulations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/simulations/</guid><description>Managing Simulations To access the Simulations section, click on Simulations in the navbar.
The Simulations view contains all the simulations you have configured and the result of their last run.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have any simulations configured yet and don&amp;rsquo;t know how to start, you can download some FrontLine pre-configured projects by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;Download sample simulations&amp;rdquo; green button.
Those samples are ready to use maven, sbt and gradle projects with proper configuration for FrontLine.</description></item><item><title>Trends</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/trends/</guid><description>Run / Trends Runs list and trends can be accessed by clicking on the icon in the simulations table.
This view contains the list of your simulation&amp;rsquo;s runs which can be filtered by name and/or status and the Trends which are displaying information between those runs. Runs table Like the result of the latest run in the simulations table you have access to the logs of the run by clicking on the icon and you can sort the table by each columns.</description></item><item><title>Reports</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/reports/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/reports/</guid><description>Reports The reports can be accessed by clicking on the icon in the simulations table or in the runs table.
This view introduce all the metrics available for a specific run. This page consists of:
The top navigation bar The timeline Tabs The run bar Charts area The summary (only for requests and groups tabs) Export PDF Top Navigation Bar The navigation bar enable you to choose the simulation time range.</description></item><item><title>Public APIs</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 13:50:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/api/</guid><description>The FrontLine API server also exposes a public API that you can use to trigger runs or fetch run results and metrics.
We also use this API for our Continuous Integration plugins and our Grafana datasource.
This API is protected with API tokens generated by FrontLine administrators through the API Tokens page.
You can access the Swagger documentation using the link FrontLine API documentation on the Documentation modal accessible on the sidenav (bottom left of the screen).</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:29:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://beta.gatling.io/docs/user/about/</guid><description>You can click on the About icon in the navigation bar to display the information about your FrontLine version and about your license.</description></item></channel></rss>